Guide to the W. Sterling Cole papers M2023
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
- Airmail The New York Times to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- ALS Richard Page to Cole, 1958 September 21; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 362)
- "Q" (Box 6, Folder 363)
- TL Cole to Mrs. Donald A. Quarles, 1959 May 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 363)
- TL Cole to Admiral Oscar A. Quihillalt, 1961 October 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 363)
- Business card, Octacilio Cunha, 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 363)
- TLS Oscar A. Quihillalt to Cole, 1958 March 21; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 363)
- TL Cole to Oscar A. Quihillalt, 1958 February 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 363)
- TL Cole to Mr. J. Ramon Quinones, 1960 May 31; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 363)
- TLS Jose Ramon Quinones to Cole, 1960 May 28; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 363)
- Bulletin, "Puerto Rican Trade Review", 1960 April; 4 pp. (Box 6, Folder 363)
- TLS Jose Ramon Quinones to Cole, 1960 April 26; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 363)
- TLS Jose Ramon Quinones, 1960 May 9; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 363)
- TL Cole to J. Ramon Quinones, 1960 April 21; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 363)
- TL Cole to Jose Ramon Quinones, 1958 January 15; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 363)
- "S" (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Yeheskel Sahar, 1960 January 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Business Card, Yeheskel Sahar, 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Charles L.T. Pichel, 1959 March 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Chas. L.T. Pichel to Cole, 1959 February 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Informational Card, "The Maltese Cross: Our Vow", 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Informational Note, "Qualifications for Knighthood", 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Announcement, "Sovereign Order of Saint John of Jerusalem: Announcement from the Convent", 1958 December 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Charles L.T. Pichel, 1958 October 8; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Chas. L.T. Pichel to Cole, 1958 August 5; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Prayer Sheet from the Sovereign Order of Saint John of Jerusalem, 1958; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Note, "Simple Vows of a Knight", 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Informational Sheet, "Revealing History of the Sovereign Order of Saint John of Jerusalem", 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Informational Note, "What is a knight?", 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Bulletin, "the Unknown in History", 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Chas. L.T. Pichel to Cole, 1958 August 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Book Review, "The Sovereign Order of Saint John of Jerusalem" by Thourot Pichel, 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Note, "Confidential message to Each member", 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Informational Note, "Cross of Honor and Merit", 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Gerard G. Shelley to Member, 1958 June 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Asher S. Chapman to the Board of Directors, 1958 June 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Charles L.T. Pichel, 1958 July 30; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Chas. L.T. Pichel to Cole, 1958 July 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Informational Note, "What is a knight?", 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Informational Note, "Our Knights", 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Pamphlet, "Famous Pioneers of the Sovereign Order of Saint John of Jerusalem", 1958; 4 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Chas. L.T. Pichel to Cole, 1958 April 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Informational Sheet, "Revealing History of the Sovereign Order of Saint John of Jerusalem", 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Informational Note, "What is a knight?", 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Charles L.T. Pichel, 1958 March 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Chas. L.T. Pichel to Cole, 1958 March 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Informational Sheet, "Revealing History of the Sovereign Order of Saint John of Jerusalem", 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Kenzo Saito, 1958 March 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Business card, Kenzo Saito. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS George Norris, Jr. to Cole, 1959 February 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Alfred Back to Cole, 1961 October 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Translation of letter from Back to Cole, 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Mayor Back, 1961 September 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Mrs. Traude Ortner, 1961 September 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Business card, Marvin Wachman, 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Booklet, "Salzburg Seminar in American Studies", 1959; 4 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to George M. Penney, 1958 May 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS George M. Penney to Cole, 1958 April 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Mrs. Halsey Sayles, 1958 February 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Mrs. Ulrike Schiller, 1958 July 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Paul Jolles, 1958 January 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Thomm Stros to Cole, 1958 May 27; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Ruth Reininghaus, 1960 October 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Picture, property of Schloss Rabenstein (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL Ruth Reininghaus to Cole, 1960 October 29; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Dr. Theodor Schmidt, 1958 February 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Mary Scrafford, 1958 December 15; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Manager of Sears Roebuck & Company, 1958 February 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Article, "Elmiran on Seawolf", 1958 October 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Telegram Cole to Laning, undated; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to His Holiness, the Pope, 1958 October 8; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Ludwig Draxler, 1959 May 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Draxler to Cole, 1959 May 8; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Draxler to Cole, 1959 April 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Dr. Draxler, 1959 March 20; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Memo from Director General, 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL AMF Overseas Corporation (President F. Chapuisht) to Cole, 1959 March 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Draxler to AMF International Corporation, 1959 February 4; 4 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Oesterreichische Studiengesellsohaft, 1959 November 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Oesterreichische Studiengesellsohaft f. Atomeneergie to Cole, 1959 October 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Henry Seligman, 1958 October 27; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Henry Seligman, 1958 May 14; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Henry Seligman to Cole, 1958 May 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Henry Seligman to Cole, 1958 February 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Henry Seligman to Cole, 1958 February 18; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Paul R. Jolles to Cole, 1958 February 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Herr Burgermeister, 1958 February 26; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Herr Wallisch, 1958 February 28; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Cole to L. Jerome Wolcott, 1958 April 29; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Zeake W. Johnson, 1958 June 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Zeake W. Johnson, Jr. to Cole, 1958 June 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Billing Statement, 1958 May 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS H. Kaufman to Cole, 1960 August 26; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to H. Kaufman, 1960 August 17; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS H. Kaufman to Cole, 1959 November 26; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to "Sirs" (Woolen Counter, Shannon Airport), 1959 November 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Dean Taylor, 1965 April 22; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Dean Taylor to Cole, 1965 April 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Unknown Sender to Dean P. Taylor, 1965 March 29; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Unknown Sender to R.J. McFalls, 1965 March 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS R.J. McFalls to Cole, 1961 September 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to R.J. McFalls, 1961 August 29; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS R.J. McFalls to Cole, 1961 February 27; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to R.J. McFalls, 1961 February 22; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to R.J. McFalls, 1958 June 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Billing Statement, 1958 June 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Billing Statement, 1957 November 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS R.J. McFalls to Cole, 1957 November 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to R.J. McFalls, 1957 November 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS R.T. Garrison to Cole, 1957 June 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Billing Statement, 1957 June 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to R.T. Garrison, 1957 June 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS R.T. Garrison to Cole, 1957 June 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Cluett Peabody, 1957 June 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL Cluett Peabody to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to R.J. McFalls, 1957 May 27; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Billing Statement, 1957 May 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Handwritten note, unknown writer, undated; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to R.J. McFalls, 1957 April 22; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS R.J. McFalls to Dean P. Taylor, 1956 January 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to R.J. McFalls, 1956 March 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS R.J. McFalls to Cole, 1956 March 14; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to R.J. McFalls, 1956 March 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to R.J. McFalls, 1956 February 20; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Harry F. Revilo, 1955 April 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Harry F. Revilo, 1955 March 29; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Dewey Short to Cole, 1958 February 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Dewey Short, 1958 January 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Joseph Shryer, 1958 December 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Joseph J. Shryer to Cole, 1958 December 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Sherman B. Shults, 1958 February 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Sherman B. Shults to Cole, 1957 December 21; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL R. Seddier to Cole, 1958 June 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Charles Silcox, 1958 January 20; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Dr. M.A.M. El Guebeily, 1959 March 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Joseph T. Simon to Cole, 1958 August 28; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Joseph T. Simon, 1958 August 26; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Joseph T. Simon to Cole, 1958 August 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Cole to Mrs. LaVauten Simmons, 1958 October 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL Mrs. LaVauten Simmons to Cole, 1958 September 27; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Richard M. Simpson, 1960 January 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Harold E. Simpson to Cole, 1960 June 23; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Avery I. Sinclair, 1959 March 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Avery I. Sinclair to Cole, undated; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to James N. Sites, 1958 February 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS James N. Sites to Cole, 1958 February 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to R. G. H. Siu, 1958 July 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Mowry Collier Skinkle, 1960 March 28; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL Mowry Collier Skinkle to Cole, 1960 March 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Article, "Bathite Honored", 1960 February 19; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Gordon K. Smith to Cole, 1957 December 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Harold H. Smith to Cole, 1959 September 22; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Harold H. Smith, 1950 September 17; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Harold H. Smith to Cole, 1959 June 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Mildred Smith, 1961 October 2; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Richard Smith, 1957 November 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Mrs. William J. Smith, 1961 August 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL Mildred S. Smith to Cole, 1961 July 22; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Mildred and Bill Smith, 1961 July 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Sepp Sokopp, 1961 November 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Sepp Sokopp to Cole, 1961 November 1; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Donald B. Sole, 1960 January 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS D.B. Sole to Cole, 1959 February 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Donald B. Sole, 1959 January 20; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Otto V. Soskuty to Cole, 1959 June 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to George G. Sowter, 1958 March 14; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS George G. Sowter to Cole, 1958 February 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Oberst Podhajaky, 1961 April 5; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Spanish Riding School to Cole, 1960 August 26; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Note, to do list, unknown author, 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Spanische Reitschule, 1960 August 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Russ Speirs to Cole, 1961 February 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL Andrew Spenser to Cole, 1958 March 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL Evelyn Speier to Cole, 1959 July 30; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Russell Spier, 1961 February 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Lawrence E. Spivak, 1958 May 1; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Lawrence E. Spivak to Cole, 1958 April 18; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL Catherine T. Squires to Miss Papworth, 1961 March 30; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS J. Duane Squires to Mary Papworth, 1961 March 28; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Business card, James Duane Squires, PH.D., 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL Unknown Sender to Unknown Recipient, undated; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Chester E. Merrow, 1961 February 27; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Chester E. Merrow to Cole, 1961 February 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to B.E.D. Hamdi, 1959 April 18; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Stanley Electric Tools, 1959 February 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Chauncey Starr, 1961 November 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Chauncey Starr, 1961 November 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Chauncey Starr to Cole, 1961 November 22; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Sydney Label to Cole, 1959 March 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Subscription clerk's receipt, 1959 March 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Invoice, The Stars and Stripes Fund, 1959 March 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL R.J. Thrush to Cole, 1959 March 9; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to R.J. Thrush, 1959 March 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Invoice, The Stars and Stripes Fund, 1959 January 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL R.J. Thrush to Cole, 1959 January 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to "Gentlemen" ("Stars and Stripes"), 1959 January 20; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Routing Slip, Stars and Stripes, undated; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Sydney Label to Cole, 1958 March 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Subscription clerk's receipt, 1958 March 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Sydney Label to Cole, 1958 August 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Sydney Label to Dr. P. Fent, 1958 August 8; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to The Editor of "Stars and Stripes", 1958 August 5; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Dr. P. Fent to Unknown Recipient, 1958 August 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS E. Blythe Stason to Cole, 1958 March 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Francis Wilcox to Cole, 1958 January 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL Wem to D.G., 1930 (?) June 6; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Article, "On War", 1957; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Edward C. Stephan, 1958 April 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS E.C. Stephan to Cole, 1958 April 15; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Interoffice Memorandum regarding Leon Steinig, 1958 May 20; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Virgil H. Gledhill to Cole, 1961 June 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Virgil H. Gledhill to Cole, 1960 July 18; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Robert B. Shuart to Cole, 1961 March 11; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL Richards to Cole, 1961 May 10; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to "Gentlemen" (American Red Cross Chapter), 1961 May 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Curtis H. Kaugelt to Cole, 1961 May 3; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Mrs. Joseph J. Neylon to Cole, 1959 September 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Robert F. Saxton to "Friend", 1959 February 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Herbert Fort to "Friend", 1958 February 13; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- AL Perry Stevenson to Cole, no year November 24; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Mr. Glockel, 1959 June 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL L.L. German to Cole, 1960 March 11; 2 pp. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Stuchly-Luchs, 1959 January 23; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Sudjarwo Tjondronegoro, 1960 October 7; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Sudjarwo to Cole, 1958 October 16; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Sullivan to karol Krackzkiewicz, 1960 January 20; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Donald Sullivan, 1959 March 26; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Donald Sullivan, 1958 August 27; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Evelyn Summers to Betty and Sterling Cole, 1959 October 12; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Miss Evelyn Summers, 1959 September 4; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS Evelyn Summers to Betty and Sterling Cole, 1959 August 31; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TL Cole to Dr. Summerskill, 1958 February 25; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Note, written by "dac" regarding Dr. Summerskill, undated; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- TLS John Summerskill to Cole, 1958 January 15; 1 p. (Box 6, Folder 364)
- Bound Documents/book: Selected Articles and Addresses by IAEA's First Director General STERLING COLE, 1957 October-1961 November (Box 6, Folder NF)